{
    "subject": "resource/J._M._E._McTaggart",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Georg_Wilhelm_Friedrich_Hegel",
    "human_readable": "J. M. E. McTaggart was influenced by Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9658998250961304,
            "question": "Can you identify a connection between Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel and J. M. E. McTaggart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.954241931438446,
            "question": "Who influenced J. M. E. McTaggart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8906950950622559,
            "question": "Name a philosopher who influenced J. M. E. McTaggart."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8250339031219482,
            "question": "Beyond Hegel, who else might have influenced J. M. E. McTaggart's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8101341128349304,
            "question": "Who is J. M. E. McTaggart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8098024129867554,
            "question": "What was the area of study of Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7534521222114563,
            "question": "What impact did Hegel's philosophy have on McTaggart's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6831484436988831,
            "question": "What philosophical ideas did J. M. E. McTaggart likely adopt from his influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6221660375595093,
            "question": "What is the significance of understanding the influences on a philosopher like J. M. E. McTaggart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40974023938179016,
            "question": "How might Hegel's ideas have shaped McTaggart's own philosophical perspectives?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=J. M. E. McTaggart was influenced by Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8728_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of understanding the influences on a philosopher like J. M. E. McTaggart?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8728_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What philosophical ideas did J. M. E. McTaggart likely adopt from his influences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8728_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Hegel's philosophy have on McTaggart's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8728_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8728_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that J. M. E. McTaggart was heavily influenced by Hegel, as he produced a large body of Hegel scholarship, including \"Studies in Hegelian Cosmology\" (1901) and later developed his own metaphysical system in \"The Nature of Existence\" (1921 & posthumously 1927), which was based on what McTaggart took to be Hegel's ontology."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"J. M. E. McTaggart was influenced by Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel.\" For instance, it mentions that McTaggart \"studied Hegel from the very beginning of his philosophical career and produced a large body of Hegel scholarship,\" indicating a significant influence of Hegel on McTaggart's work and philosophy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}